The story of a man who believes in heroes, in a
world where the anti-hero is king.
Hitman Hart: Wrestling with Shadows is a documentary,
tv movie film directed by Paul Jay.
This documentary follows superstar Bret Hart during his last year in the WWF.
The film documents the tensions that resulted in The Montreal Screwjob, one of the most controversial events in the history of professional wrestling, in which
Vince McMahon, Shawn Micheals, and others, legitimately conspired behind the scenes to go against the script and remove Bret Hart as champion.
Self, played by Bret Hart.
Self, played by Owen Hart.
Self, played by Vince McMahon.
Self, played by Steve Austin.
Shawn Michaels, played by Michael Hickenbottom.
Self, played by Mick Foley.
Hitman Hart: Wrestling with Shadows is a 1998 Canadian documentary
film directed, produced and written by Paul Jay.
It follows Bret "The Hitman" Hart during his last year in the WWF, from his World Wrestling Federation Championship victory at SummerSlam to
his final match with the company and the infamous Montreal Screwjob at the pay-per-view Survivor Series on November 9, 1997.
The film explores themes of sports, wrestling, wrestler.